<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Yoga Fitness App</string>
    <string name="pose1">    Step 1:- Start in the push-up position with your arms completely straight and directly beneath your shoulders.\n\n
                             Step 2:- Your body should form a straight line from your shoulders to your ankles. \n\n
                             Step 3:- Squeeze your abs, lift one foot off the floor and bring your knee up towards your chest while keeping your body in as straight of a line as possible. \n\n
                             Step 4:- Return to the starting position and repeat the movement with your opposite leg.. </string>
    <string name="pose2">    Step 1:- Lie flat on your mat with knees bent and feet on the mat. Hands at the base ofyour head and elbows pointed out. Using your abdominals bring your head and shoulders off the mat and come up into a crunch, then lower with control. </string>
    <string name="pose3">    Step 1:- This movement is performed with a bench and a foot stool.\n\n
                             Step 2:- Place a bench behind yourself and rest on it with your hands. Place your legs straight out in front of you. You may also place them at an elevated level as shown above.\n\n
                             Step 3:- Begin with arms in a fully. Slowly bend at your elbows keeping the rest of your body straight. Be sure to keep your elbows back and close together.\n\n
                             Step 4:- Dip down until your arms form a 90 degree angle and you feel a stretch in the triceps.\n\n
                             Step 5:- Slowly extend your arms raising your body back up. Pause and contract your triceps muscles at the top. Pause and repeat the movement.</string>
    <string name="pose4">    Step 1:- Lie flat on the floor with your lower back pressed to the ground (pull your navel in to also target your deep abs). \n\n
                             Step 2:- Put your hands behind your head, then bring your knees in towards your Chest and lift your shoulder blades off the ground, but be sure not to pull on your neck.\n\n
                             Step 3:-Straighten your right leg out to about a 4S-degree angle to the ground while turning your upper body to the left, bringing your right elbow towards the left knee.\n\n
                             Step 4:- Make sure your rib cage is moving and hotjust your elbows. Now switch sides and do the same motion on the other side to complete onerep. </string>
    <string name="pose5">   Step 1:- Lay down with your hands to your sides for support. \n\n
                             Step 2:- Raise your legs so they are off the ground, keeping the abdominals tight.\n\n
                             Step 3:- Slowly raise your legs 90 degrees, contracting the abdominal muscles. Slowly return to starting position. Do not touch the floor with your feet.\n\n
                            </string>


    <string name="pose6">    Step 1:- Lie on your back on an exercise mat. With your arms straight at your sides, bend your knees and place your feet flat on the floor between18 and 24 inches apart.\n\n
                             Step 2:- Breathing out, crunch your ab slightly upward and sideways to the right a couple of inches until your right hand touches your right heel.\n\n
                             Step 3:- Hold brief|y and then return to your starting position while inhaling. Repeat on the left side. </string>
    <string name="pose7">    Step 1:- You can perform straight-leg crunches by lying face up on the floor with your legs straight and then moving your upper body as you would for a standard bent-knee crunch.\n\n
                             Step 2:- Alternatively, lie on your back, raise your legs so they are perpendicular to the floor and then perform the standard crunching motion with your torso.
                             </string>
    <string name="pose8">    Step 1:- Lie down on the floor placing your feet either under something that Will not move or by having a partner hold them. Your legs should be bent at the kneesPlace your hands behind your head and lock them together by claspihg your fingers. This is the starting position.\n\n
                             Step 2:- Elevate your upper body so that it creates an imaginary V-shape with your thighs. Breathe out when performing this part of the exercise.\n\n
                             Step 3:- Once you feel the contraction for a second, lower your upper body back down to the starting position while inhahng. \n\n
                             Step 4:- Repeat for the recommended amount of repetitions.
                            </string>
    <string name="pose9">    Step 1:- Lying on the back,lift stright leg,extend opposite hand to touch toe. \n\n
                             Step 2:- Please,return,alternate inhale down,exhale up at toe touch.
                            </string>
    <string name="pose10">    Step 1:- High Plank position then slowly rotate your torso to the side raising your arm till it gets ihlihe with the other one. \n\n
                             Step 2:- Then return to the initial position.
                            </string>
    <string name="pose11">    Step 1:- Lie on the floor with elbows directly beneath your shoulders and legs fully extended.\n\n
                             Step 2:- Raise your torso into the air until it makes a straight line from your shoulders to your ankles. Tighten your stomach, squeeze your butt.
                            </string>
    <string name="pose12">    Step 1:- Lie down on the floor placing your feet either under something that will not move or by having a partner hold them. Your legs should be bent at the knees. Elevate your upper body so that it creates an imaginary V-shape with your thighs. \n\n
                             Step 2:- Your arms should be fully extended in front of you perpendicular to your torso and with the hands clasped. This is the starting position.\n\n
                             Step 3:- This is the starting position. Twist your torso to the right side until your arms are parallel with the floor while breathing out. \n\n
                             Step 4:- Hold the contraction for a second and move back to the starting position while breathing out. Now move to the opposite side performing the same techniques you applied to the right side. Repeat for the recommended amount of repetitions.
                            </string>
    <string name="pose13">    Step 1:- Lie on your back with your knees bent, feet flat and hip width. \n\n
                             Step 2:- Lower your pelvis 2 inches from the floor. Squeeze your glutes and lift your pelvis back to bridge position.

                            </string>
    <string name="pose14">    Step 1:- Lie facedown on the floor with your arms extended in front of you and your leg extended behind you. \n\n
                             Step 2:- In one movement,engage your glutes and lower back to raise your arms,legs,and chest off the floor.\n\n
                             Step 3:- Hold for a count,then slowly return to the starting position.
                            </string>
    <string name="pose15">   Step 1:- Stand, extend arms 90° to sides, bend forward 90° at waist.\n\n
                             Step 2:- Looking at the floor, rotate torso to touch hand to foot, rotate for other hand. \n\n
                             Step 3:- Head will follow chest action. </string>
    <string name="pose16">1.Stand straight with your feet shoulder-width apart.\n\n
                          2. Bend over and touch the floor with the palms of your hands.\n\n
                          3. Walk your hands out, as far as you can while keeping your legs straight, and pause.\n\n
                          4. Walk back up to the starting position and repeat until the set is complete…</string>

    <string name="pose17">1. Start in a push up position with your legs extended back and the hands below the shoulders.\n\n
                          2. Place your left forearm on the mat, with the elbow directly under the shoulder, and start bending your right elbow until your chest is just above the floor.\n\n
                          3. Push back to the starting position, repeat, and then switch sides…</string>

    <string name="pose18">1.Stand with your feet in a wide stance and with your toes pointing out to the sides.\n\n
                          2. Squat to the right, going as low as it feels comfortable.\n\n
                          3. Return to the starting position and repeat on the left side…</string>

    <string name="pose19">1.Start in downward dog pose with your arms and legs straight and your hips up and back.\n\n
                          2. Push off with your toes, kick your legs up and bend the knees.\n\n
                          3. Land on your toes with your knees slightly bent.\n\n
                          4. Repeat until the set is complete…</string>

    <string name="pose20">1.Start in a push up position, with your hands under your shoulders and your legs extended back.\n\n
                          2. Start bending your elbows and lower your chest until it’s just above the floor.\n\n
                          3. As you push back to the starting position, lift your hips, and touch your left ankle with your right hand.\n\n
                          4. Return to the push up position and repeat on the opposite side.\n\n
                          5. Keep alternating sides until the set is complete..</string>

    <string name="pose21">1.Sit on the mat with your feet together, place your hands behind you with your fingers facing forward, bend your knees and let your thighs fall open.\n\n
                          2. Straighten your arms as you press your hips up and bring both knees together.\n\n
                          3. Bend your elbows and lower your body back to the starting position.\n\n
                          4. Repeat until the set is complete…</string>

    <string name="pose22">1.Lie on your back with your arms by your sides, raise the legs toward the ceiling, bend the knees and bring the soles of your feet together (like a frog).\n\n
                          2. Extend the legs out to the sides as far as possible, and then squeeze the inner thighs to bring them together.\n\n
                          3. Return to the frog position and repeat until the set is complete..</string>

    <string name="pose23">1.Start with your feet a little wider than shoulder-width apart, transfer your weight to your right leg and lift your left foot off the floor.\n\n
                          2.Bend your right knee, lower your hips back and squat.\n\n
                          3.Stand up, then kick your left leg back.\n\n
                          4.Lower your left foot to a few inches off the floor and repeat for the duration of the set.\n\n
                          5.Return to the starting position and repeat with the opposite leg..</string>

    <string name="pose24">1.Stand with your feet hip-width apart and hold a dumbbell in your right hand.\n\n
                          2. Take a big step back with your left leg, cross it behind your right leg, and lunge.\n\n
                          3. As you stand up, kick your left leg out to the side and raise the dumbbell to shoulder height.\n\n
                          4. Repeat and then switch sides…</string>

    <string name="pose25">1.Start in a plank position with your body in a straight line, your wrists under your shoulders, and your feet shoulder-width apart.\n\n
                          2.Extend one leg and the opposite arm at the same time.\n\n
                          3.Pause for 3 to 5 seconds, return to the starting position, and switch sides.\n\n
                          4.Continue alternating sides until the set is complete..</string>

    <string name="pose26">1.Stand with your feet in a wide stance, your toes pointing out to the sides and your hands behind your head.\n\n
                          2. Bend your knees, press your hips back and bring your right elbow toward your right knee.\n\n
                         3. Repeat on the left side and keep alternating sides until the set is complete....</string>

    <string name="pose27">1.Stand with your feet in a wide stance, your toes pointing out to the sides, and hold a dumbbell in each hand with your palms facing up.\n\n
                          2.Squat until your thighs are parallel to the floor, and lower the dumbbells close to your knees.\n\n
                          3.Stand up and bring the dumbbells together in front of your chest.\n\n
                          4.Repeat until the set is complete..</string>
    <string name="tips">1.Drink 10 to 12 glass of water daily.\n\n
                        2.No need to do cardio daily,you can do it 3 to 4 times a day.\n\n
                        3.Take every meal properly so that your metabolism works fast but avoid junk.\n\n
                        4.Do workout daily.\n\n
                        5.Keep track of calories and food intake per day..\n\n
                        6.A child should take 1000-1400 calories per day and an adult should take 2000-3000 calories per day.\n\n
                        7.Get enough sleep.\n\n
                        8.Stay Motivated.\n\n
                        9. Avoid anger and frustration and walking and jogging  in fresh air will help you in this case.\n\n
                        10.Stay happy and positive.Your life is for you so dont waste it
    </string>


</resources>